momswithapps.com 2015-08-02

# Moms With Apps

_Effective as of June 12, 2013._

General Statement of Privacy

ACT | The App Association respects the privacy of its members and of those who visit this site. Subject to the provisions of applicable laws, any information you submit to the ACT will not be used in any manner to which you have not consented.

Personally Identifiable Information

We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information about you on momswithapps.com without your knowledge or action. Personally Identifiable Information is collected through the membership registration form, e-mail newsletter registration, legislator contact and/or other forms. This information includes, but is not limited to your e-mail address and zip code. You should be aware that if you disclose any information on an open forum that is hosted by the ACT, others may collect that information to send you unsolicited information from outside the ACT, or for other purposes.

Use of Personally Identifiable Information

It is our general policy not to make Personally Identifiable Information available to anyone other than our employees, staff, and agents. We will never sell your e-mail address or other Personally Identifiable Information.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes, but is not limited to, information we automatically collect on your use and/or actions on our Web site (e.g., user traffic patterns, page views on the Web site, click-through rates, search terms that users enter into our search utility). In addition, when a visitor arrives at our site, we collect the IP address, operating system, and browser software used. An IP address (which is not the same as an e-mail address) can tell us the user’s internet service provider and, based on that, can suggest the geographic location of the connection. ACT recognizes that certain user information of a key demographic nature (e.g., race, age, gender, national origin, income), while Non-Personally Identifiable Information, is still of a sensitive nature to users.

As a general matter, the ACT does not collect demographic information about you through regular use of momswithapps.com. However, in recognition of the sensitive nature of such information, in the event the ACT comes into possession of such information, whether through your voluntary submission of such information in response to a special feature on the Web site or by receiving such information from any of our business partners, such information shall, when coupled with any of your Personally Identifiable Information, itself be deemed to be Personally Identifiable Information and treated by the ACT as such.

Use of Non-personally identifiable information

As a general matter, Non-Personally Identifiable Information helps us determine how the momswithapps.com is being used, helps us identify popular areas of the Web site, and helps determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities regarding the Web site. In some cases it may be shared with a third party contracted by the ACT in the course of doing so.

Use of Cookies

If momswithapps.com uses cookies (i.e., a small data file that our Web site writes to a user’s hard drive) to help track your usage of our site, including what advertising you have seen. momswithapps.com’s cookies enable us to provide you with services you may request.

You can refuse our cookies by turning them off in your browser (for more information on how to do this, please refer to your browser’s documentation). You do not need to have cookies turned on in your browser to use ACTn.org; however, without cookies certain of the automated functions and features of the site will not be available to you. We also use cookies to measure the click through rate on e-mails delivered.

Third Party use of personal information

Momswithapps.com may contain links to other Internet Web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, including such sites’ use of any information.

Security

You understand and agree that “perfect” security does not exist anywhere, including on the Internet. Information you send to this site, including email messages, will not be encrypted unless we advise you otherwise.

Other Services

You may be able to access certain information related to third parties at the Site, or via links or clickthroughs from the Site, regarding the goods or services of third parties. You understand and agree that your access to or use of those services is a matter entirely between you and the associated third parties, and the ACT shall have no liability whatsoever for any such access or use.

Notice to Parents or guardians

We want to help you protect your child’s privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their personal information while using the Internet. In particular, ACT does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for ACT or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Site or ACT. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us via the “Contact Us” link on the Site. We recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet

Opting Out

To opt out of receiving information, please contact us in one of the following ways:

1\. Use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our e-mails.

2\. Send an e-mail to info@momswithapps.com.

3\. Send a written request to:  

> Moms With Apps  
>  1401 K St. NW, Suite 502  
>  Washington, DC 20005

You may also write to us at any time should you wish have Personally Identifiable Information about yourself that we have collected removed from our database.

Governing Law

This Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of ACT and any dispute arising out of or relating thereto will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the District of Columbia, without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located within the District of Columbia to resolve any legal matter arising from this Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of ACT. Notwithstanding the foregoing, you agree that ACT shall be allowed to apply for injunctive relief (or an equivalent type of urgent legal relief) in any jurisdiction. ACT makes no representation that this Privacy Policy and such practices comply with the laws of any other country. Visitors who use the Site and reside outside of the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is available at all times to all users of momswithapps.com at http://momswithapps.com/privacy Any material changes to this privacy policy will be communicated to users through this Web page. Users are responsible for making use of this resource to stay up to date on this privacy policy.
